<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CHANDIGARH TOURISM</string>
    <string name="exit">LOGOUT</string>
    <string name="aboutapp">ABOUT APP</string>
    <string name="open">OPEN</string>
    <string name="close">CLOSE</string>
    <string name="home">Chandigarh is the best-planned city in India, with architecture which is world-renowned, and a quality of life, which is unparalleled. As the capital of the states of Punjab and Haryana, and the Union Territory of Chandigarh it is a prestigious city. The face of modern India, Chandigarh, is the manifestation of a dream that Pt. Jawahar Lal Nehru envisaged and Le Corbusier executed. Serenity and a city are two diametrically opposite concepts, which however, get belied in the City Beautiful. Chandigarh is a rare epitome of modernization co-existing with natures preservation. It is here that the trees and plants are as much a part of the construction plans as the buildings and the roads. Indias first planned city, is a rich, prosperous, spic and span, green city rightly called  THE CITY BEAUTIFUL .</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="rock">The Rock Garden of Chandigarh is a sculpture garden in Chandigarh, India. It is also known as Nek Chands Rock Garden after its founder Nek Chand, a government official who started the garden secretly in his spare time in 1957. Today it is spread over an area of 40 acres (161874.25 m²). It is completely built of industrial and home waste and thrown-away items.[1][2]It is near Sukhna Lake.[3] It consists of man-made interlinked waterfalls and many other sculptures that have been made of scrap and other kinds of wastes (bottles, glasses, bangles, tiles, ceramic pots, sinks, electrical waste,brokenpipes, etc.) which are placed in walled paths.</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="valley">Chandigarh is full of greenery, with the various theme gardens standing for the beauty and spirit of the city. Le Corbusier, the architect of the city, retained the eroded valley of a seasonal rivulet on the original site of the city and sculptured it into a linear park. Eight kilometers in length, the park starts from Sector 1 in the north and leaves Chandigarh at its southern-most edge, in sector 53. In the Master Plan of Le Corbuiser, where he had planned the city analogous to a human body, the leisure valley and gardens were planned to form the lungs of the city. Out of the total area of 20,000 acres acquired for the first phase, about 2,000 acres was meant for the development of parks. These parks and gardens are collectively known as the Leisure Valley of Chandigarh. Each of the parks and gardens in the city bears a different name and boasts of some or other specialty.</string>
    <string name="le">Le Corbusier Centre has been set up by the Chandigarh Administration, at the old Sector 19 office of the city’s architect, Le Corbusier. The Swiss-French architect used the office while conceptualizing the city almost six decades ago.The Centre displays and exhibits the life and works of Le Corbusier, so that tourists and future generations may be able to acquaint themselves with the rich cultural heritage of the city.The main aim of the Centre would be preservation, interpretation, research, display of the works and legacy of Le Corbusier.</string>
    <string name="botanical">A botanical garden is generally a well kept park which contains many different kinds of plants labeled with their botanical names. They can contain collections of special types of plants, such as cacti, herb gardens, plants of certain parts of the world. Some of these collections need to be kept in greenhouses, such as tropical plants, alpine plants or other exotic plants.In botanic gardens, seeds or cuttings are collected from species in the wild and then used to build up a population of plants from which, one day, some plants may be reintroduced to their natural habitats. Tissue culture can often help to produce many plants from just a few specimens.</string>
    <string name="rose">Rose garden of Chandigarh, India is the largest of its kind in Asia. Named after Indias former President, Zakir Hussain, this beautiful garden was set up in 1967 with the support of Chandigarhs first Chief Commissioner, late Dr M S Randhawa. Chandigarh rose garden contains more than 17,000 plants. There are nearly 1,600 varieties of roses over there. It is a spacious garden covering an area of 27 acres. Dr. Zakir rose garden not just consists of the gorgeous roses, but also trees of medicinal value. Some of the medicinal plants that can be spotted here are bel, bahera, harar, camphor and yellow gulmohar. Rose garden serves as the venue for hosting the annual festival of gardens, a major cultural event of the city.</string>
</resources>

